question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "On average, at least 1 person is killed by a drunk driver in the United States every hour.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "French is an official language in Canada.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]

# print(question_data[0]["text"])
# print(question_data[0]["answer"])
